Eugene Opie Papers ca.1919-1971 Mss.B.Op3
American Philosophical Society
- Correspondence
  - U.S. Naval Intelligence (Box 57)
  - U.S. Office of Scientific Research and Development (Box 57)
  - U.S. Selective Service (Box 57)
  - U.S. Veterans Bureau - Tuberculosis lectures (Box 57)
  - University of California. Social Sciences Project (Box 57)
  - University of Cincinnati. College of Medicine (Box 57)
  - University of Edinburgh (Box 57)
  - University of Minnesota - Mayo Foundation affiliation (Box 57)
  - University of Pennsylvania (Box 58)
    - Brief for plan of celebration (Box 58)
    - Department of pathology (Box 59)
    - General alumni society (Box 59)
    - Medical school (Box 59)
    - Medical celebration committee (Box 59)
    - Medical celebration committee, Minutes (Box 59)
    - New Medical laboratory (Box 59)
    - Personnel suggested for pathology (Box 59)
    - Report of provost (Box 59)
    - Tucker, C.E. Report on dedicatory ceremonies (Box 59)
    - Veterinary school (Box 59)
  - University of Sydney (Box 59)
  - University of Wisconsin. Medical School (Box 59)
  - Unknown (Box 59)
  - Vaccine S (Box 59)
  - Vanderbilt Univ., Phi Beta Pi lecture (Box 59)
  - Van Es, L (Box 59)
  - Van Slyke, Donald D (Box 59)
  - Van Wesep, H B (Box 59)
  - Vargas, Luis (Box 59)
  - Vasahelyi, John (Box 59)
  - Veeder, Borden S (Box 59)
  - Vera, Mrs. M. (Box 59)
  - Verder, B. S. (Box 60)
  - Vijil, Fernandez (Box 60)
  - Vincent, George E (Box 60)
  - Virgin, Germund (Box 60)
  - Virginia Tuberculosis Association (Box 60)
  - Vischow, R (Box 60)
  - Voegtlin, Carl (Box 60)
  - Vogl, Alfred (Box 60)
  - Volksgesundheit, "Zeitschrift fär Soziale Hygiene" (Box 60)
  - Von Glahn, William C (Box 60)
  - Von Noorden (Box 60)
  - Wade, Leo J (Box 60)
  - Wagener, E H (Box 60)
  - Wagner, C E (Box 60)
  - Wahmann, C Harry (Box 60)
  - Walcott, Frederic C (Box 60)
  - Walker, Helen Scott (Box 60)
  - Walker, W J (Box 60)
  - Wallis, Allan D (Box 60)
  - Walsh, Groesbeck (Box 60)
  - Walsh, Joseph (Box 60)
  - Walsh, L S N (Box 60)
  - Walsh, L.S.N. The effect of horse, ass, mule serum (Box 60)
  - Walsh, L.S.N. Natural auto and iso spermotoxins in guinea pig serum (Box 60)
  - Walsh, Newman (Box 60)
  - Walsh, Williamina Rayne (Box 60)
  - Walther Printing House (Box 60)
  - Walton, Charles H.S. "A Study of the Racial Incidence of Tuberculosis in Manitoba" (Box 60)
  - War Department, Army medical museum and libraryWard, Ernest (Box 60)
  - Waring, James J (Box 60)
  - Warren, Andrew J (Box 60)
  - Warren, Shields (Box 60)
  - Washburn, Benjamin E (Box 60)
  - Washburn, B.E. Report of cooperative public health work in Jamaica (Box 60)
  - Washburn, B.E. Tuberculosis in Jamaica (Box 60)
  - Washington University (Box 60)
  - Washington University (Box 60)
    - Dispensary committee (Box 60)
    - Hospital (Box 60)
    - Medical School (Box 61)
    - Medical school - budgets (Box 61)
    - Medical School - Dept. of Obstetrics and Gynecology (Box 61)
    - Medical School - early offer Equipment History (Box 61)
  - Waterman, Alan (Box 61)
  - Watt, M H (Box 61)
  - Watts, H F R (Box 61)
  - Watts, James W (Box 61)
  - Waverly Press, Inc. (Box 61)
  - Wayson, N E (Box 61)
  - Weaver, George H (Box 61)
  - Webb, Gerald B (Box 61)
  - Weber-Parkes Award (Box 61)
  - Webster, Leslie T (Box 61)
  - Webster, Ralph W (Box 61)
  - Wehrle, Hans (Box 61)
  - Weinberg (Box 61)
  - Weinzirl, John (Box 61)
  - Weir, John M (Box 61)
  - Weir, J.M. Jamaican diary (Box 61)
  - Weiss, Charles (Box 61)
  - Weiss, Edward (Box 61)
  - Weiss, Philip (Box 61)
  - Welch, William Henry (Box 61)
  - Weldon, Beulah (Box 61)
  - Welfare Hospital: research service (Box 61)
  - Weller, Carl V (Box 61)
  - Weller, Doris A (Box 61)
  - Wells, Clifford W (Box 62)
  - Wells, C. W. (Box 62)
    - Semi-annual report (Box 62)
    - Tuberculosis in Jamaica. Reports (Box 62)
    - Epidemiology of tuberculosis in Kingston (Box 62)
  - Wells, H Gideon (Box 62)
  - Werne, Jacob (Box 62)
  - Westbrook, F F (Box 62)
  - Western Reserve University (Box 62)
  - Weston, Eugene L (Box 62)
  - Westwater, John Ovenstone (Box 62)
  - Westwater, J. A Note on the serum sodium levels in patients (Box 62)
  - Wheeler, George W (Box 62)
  - Whipple, George H (Box 62)
  - White, H L (Box 62)
  - White, Park J (Box 62)
  - White, William Charles (Box 62)
  - White House Conference on child health and protection (Box 62)
  - White House Conference: committee on growth and development (Box 62)
  - White House Conference: effects of disease upon growth and development (Box 62)
  - Whitman, R C (Box 62)
  - Whitmore, Eugene R (Box 62)
  - Whitney, Caroline (Box 62)
  - Whitney, Jessamine S. "High Points of Attack" (Box 62)
  - White, William Charles (Box 62)
  - Who's Who in America (Box 62)
  - Who's Important in Medicine (Box 62)
  - Who's Who in the East (Box 62)
  - Wie Bewahren Wir Uns vor Tuberkulose? (Box 62)
  - Wiesner, Dorothy E (Box 62)
  - Wilber, Lyman (Box 62)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman (Box 62)
  - Wilkinson, W Camac (Box 62)
  - William Pepper Medical Society (Box 62)
  - Williams, Ennion G (Box 62)
  - Williams, Linsly R (Box 62)
  - Williams, Ruth C (Box 62)
  - Williams, W C (Box 62)
  - Williams and Wilkins Company (Box 62)
  - Willis, H S (Box 62)
  - Wilson, Basil M (Box 62)
  - Wilson, Edwin B (Box 62)
  - Wilson, J Walter (Box 62)
  - Wilson, Julius L (Box 62)
  - Wilson, Louis B (Box 62)
  - Wilt, A., & Sons Company (Box 62)
  - Winn, Annah (Box 62)
  - Winston, Rudolph (Box 62)
  - Winternitz, M C (Box 62)
  - Wisconsin Anti-Tuberculosis Association (Box 62)
  - Wisconsin Medical Alumni Association (Box 62)
  - Wise, Byrd (Box 62)
  - Wissler, Robert W (Box 62)
  - Withers, Sanford (Box 62)
  - Witter, Margaret (Box 62)
  - Wolbach, S. B. (Box 62)
  - "Little Hookworm", Wolcott, Mary (Box 62)
  - Wolff, Georg (Box 62)
  - Wood, F. C. (Box 62)
  - Woodruff, Clinton Rogers (Box 62)
  - Woods, Archie (Box 62)
  - Woods, E. Bryant (Box 62)
  - Woody, McIver (Box 62)
  - Woollcott, Alexander (Box 62)
  - World Biography (Box 62)
  - World Who's Who in Science (Box 62)
  - Worthington, Sara J. (Box 62)
  - Wright, Sir Almroth (Box 62)
  - Wright, George A. Pemberton (Box 62)
  - Wright, Henry C. (Box 62)
  - Wriston, Henry M. (Box 62)
  - Wu, S. C. (Box 62)
  - Wyllie, H. R. (Box 62)
  - X-Ray nodular shadows (Box 62)
  - Yale Judiciary Committee (Box 62)
  - Yale Medical Alumni Association (Box 62)
  - Yale University (Box 62)
  - Yates, John Laurence (Box 62)
  - Yellow fever (Box 62)
  - Yi, C. L. (Box 62)
  - Yochelson, Ellis L. (Box 62)
  - Young, Lionel I. C. (Box 62)
  - Young, Marjorie (Box 62)
  - Yutang, Lin (Box 62)
  - Zander, Ernst (Box 62)
  - Zeckwer, Isolde T. (Box 62)
  - Ziegler, Edwin E. (Box 62)
  - Zeitschrift fär Tuberculose (Box 62)
  - Zimmerman, John E. (Box 62)
  - Zinsser, Hans (Box 62)